jobsdecade.com 2011-04-25

# Jobsdecade.com :: Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our job portal called www.jobsdecade.com  
This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted clearly on the website. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**_The Security of Your Information_**  
jobsdecade.com protects the security of your user name and password during transmission by using secure sockets layer (SSL) software, which encrypts such information. 

**_Cookies_**  
Cookies are small text files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit our portal. jobsdecade.com uses cookies to improve the portal and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. 

**_Third Parties_**  
jobsdecade.com DOES NOT rent or sell personal information it collects about the user to third parties without the user's explicit permission, except in the case of acquisitions as explained below. 

**_Acquisitions_**  
As jobsdecade.com continues to develop its business, like any normal business it acquires or sells its assets. One such non tangible asset is the information about the user that we collect. The same might be transferred in the event of jobsdecade.com being acquired. 

**_Compliance with Laws_**  
jobsdecade.com reserves the right to release personal information when it receives a request for the same from competent law enforcing authorities in India or any other country in which it stores the same. 

**_User Rights_**  
For the user, since this service is currently being provided on a free of cost basis, jobsdecade.com gives no guarantee of server uptime or applications working properly. All is done on a best effort basis. 

**_Contact_**  
If you have any questions about this section or the practices of this portal feel free send a mail to [contact@jobsdecade.com](mailto:contact@jobsdecade.com)
